{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.vow.asc.all.stat.noShow.25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259557763","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259557762"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_190532"," gameId":" ce3d9628-901a-4b84-b211-1bdb5e10c6cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.vow.asc.all.stat.noShow.25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_A_U-E-A"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.vow.asc.all.stat.noShow.25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259561024","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259561023"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_190532"," gameId":" ce3d9628-901a-4b84-b211-1bdb5e10c6cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.vow.asc.all.stat.noShow.25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_E_E-I-O"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.vow.asc.all.stat.noShow.25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259564310","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259564309"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_190532"," gameId":" ce3d9628-901a-4b84-b211-1bdb5e10c6cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.vow.asc.all.stat.noShow.25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_I_I-U-E"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.vow.asc.all.stat.noShow.25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259567228","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259567228"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_190532"," gameId":" ce3d9628-901a-4b84-b211-1bdb5e10c6cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.vow.asc.all.stat.noShow.25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_O_O-E-U"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.vow.asc.all.stat.noShow.25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259569949","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259569949"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_190532"," gameId":" ce3d9628-901a-4b84-b211-1bdb5e10c6cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.vow.asc.all.stat.noShow.25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_U_U-E-O"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.vow.asc.all.stat.noShow.25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259570840","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259570840"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_190532"," gameId":" ce3d9628-901a-4b84-b211-1bdb5e10c6cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.vow.asc.all.stat.noShow.25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_U_U-E-O"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259583876","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259583876"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_190532"," gameId":" f5502bce-a3fd-4f2e-a286-c7967c5c81f3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UPINDE"," userResponse":" UPINDE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259584309","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259584309"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_190532"," gameId":" f5502bce-a3fd-4f2e-a286-c7967c5c81f3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UNA"," userResponse":" UNA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259584792","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259584792"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_190532"," gameId":" f5502bce-a3fd-4f2e-a286-c7967c5c81f3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANGI"," userResponse":" RANGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259585434","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259585434"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_190532"," gameId":" f5502bce-a3fd-4f2e-a286-c7967c5c81f3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SABA"," userResponse":" SABA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259588462","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259588462"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_190532"," gameId":" f5502bce-a3fd-4f2e-a286-c7967c5c81f3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya kwanza ni nyekundu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANGI"," userResponse":" RANGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259588555","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259588555"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_190532"," gameId":" f5502bce-a3fd-4f2e-a286-c7967c5c81f3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya kwanza ni nyekundu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259589409","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259589408"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_190532"," gameId":" f5502bce-a3fd-4f2e-a286-c7967c5c81f3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya kwanza ni nyekundu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259589821","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259589821"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_190532"," gameId":" f5502bce-a3fd-4f2e-a286-c7967c5c81f3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya kwanza ni nyekundu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259590644","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259590644"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_190532"," gameId":" f5502bce-a3fd-4f2e-a286-c7967c5c81f3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya kwanza ni nyekundu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYEKUNDU"," userResponse":" NYEKUNDU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259593639","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259593639"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_190532"," gameId":" f5502bce-a3fd-4f2e-a286-c7967c5c81f3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kweyu amevalia shati la rangi nyekundu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWEYU"," userResponse":" KWEYU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259594682","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259594682"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_190532"," gameId":" f5502bce-a3fd-4f2e-a286-c7967c5c81f3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kweyu amevalia shati la rangi nyekundu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMEVALIA"," userResponse":" AMEVALIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259595374","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259595374"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_190532"," gameId":" f5502bce-a3fd-4f2e-a286-c7967c5c81f3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kweyu amevalia shati la rangi nyekundu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHATI"," userResponse":" SHATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259595567","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259595567"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_190532"," gameId":" f5502bce-a3fd-4f2e-a286-c7967c5c81f3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kweyu amevalia shati la rangi nyekundu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LA"," userResponse":" LA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259596141","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259596141"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_190532"," gameId":" f5502bce-a3fd-4f2e-a286-c7967c5c81f3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kweyu amevalia shati la rangi nyekundu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANGI"," userResponse":" RANGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259596933","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259596933"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_190532"," gameId":" f5502bce-a3fd-4f2e-a286-c7967c5c81f3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kweyu amevalia shati la rangi nyekundu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYEKUNDU"," userResponse":" NYEKUNDU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259599937","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259599937"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_190532"," gameId":" f5502bce-a3fd-4f2e-a286-c7967c5c81f3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya pili ni ya chungwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANGI"," userResponse":" RANGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259600040","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259600040"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_190532"," gameId":" f5502bce-a3fd-4f2e-a286-c7967c5c81f3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya pili ni ya chungwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259600803","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259600803"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_190532"," gameId":" f5502bce-a3fd-4f2e-a286-c7967c5c81f3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya pili ni ya chungwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PILI"," userResponse":" PILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259601315","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259601315"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_190532"," gameId":" f5502bce-a3fd-4f2e-a286-c7967c5c81f3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya pili ni ya chungwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259601508","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259601508"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_190532"," gameId":" f5502bce-a3fd-4f2e-a286-c7967c5c81f3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya pili ni ya chungwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259602180","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259602180"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_190532"," gameId":" f5502bce-a3fd-4f2e-a286-c7967c5c81f3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya pili ni ya chungwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUNGWA"," userResponse":" CHUNGWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259604969","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259604968"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_190532"," gameId":" f5502bce-a3fd-4f2e-a286-c7967c5c81f3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hili ni chungwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HILI"," userResponse":" HILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259605191","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259605191"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_190532"," gameId":" f5502bce-a3fd-4f2e-a286-c7967c5c81f3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hili ni chungwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259605894","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259605894"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_190532"," gameId":" f5502bce-a3fd-4f2e-a286-c7967c5c81f3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hili ni chungwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUNGWA"," userResponse":" CHUNGWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259608913","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259608913"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_190532"," gameId":" f5502bce-a3fd-4f2e-a286-c7967c5c81f3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya tatu ni manjano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANGI"," userResponse":" RANGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259609026","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259609026"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_190532"," gameId":" f5502bce-a3fd-4f2e-a286-c7967c5c81f3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya tatu ni manjano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259609708","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259609708"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_190532"," gameId":" f5502bce-a3fd-4f2e-a286-c7967c5c81f3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya tatu ni manjano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TATU"," userResponse":" TATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259610191","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259610191"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_190532"," gameId":" f5502bce-a3fd-4f2e-a286-c7967c5c81f3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya tatu ni manjano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259611003","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259611003"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_190532"," gameId":" f5502bce-a3fd-4f2e-a286-c7967c5c81f3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya tatu ni manjano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANJANO"," userResponse":" MANJANO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259614018","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259614018"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_190532"," gameId":" f5502bce-a3fd-4f2e-a286-c7967c5c81f3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yai pingu lina rangi ya manjano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAI"," userResponse":" YAI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259614650","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259614650"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_190532"," gameId":" f5502bce-a3fd-4f2e-a286-c7967c5c81f3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yai pingu lina rangi ya manjano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PINGU"," userResponse":" PINGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259615382","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259615382"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_190532"," gameId":" f5502bce-a3fd-4f2e-a286-c7967c5c81f3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yai pingu lina rangi ya manjano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LINA"," userResponse":" LINA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259616094","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259616094"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_190532"," gameId":" f5502bce-a3fd-4f2e-a286-c7967c5c81f3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yai pingu lina rangi ya manjano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANGI"," userResponse":" RANGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259616226","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259616226"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_190532"," gameId":" f5502bce-a3fd-4f2e-a286-c7967c5c81f3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yai pingu lina rangi ya manjano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259617068","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259617068"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_190532"," gameId":" f5502bce-a3fd-4f2e-a286-c7967c5c81f3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yai pingu lina rangi ya manjano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANJANO"," userResponse":" MANJANO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259620204","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259620204"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_190532"," gameId":" f5502bce-a3fd-4f2e-a286-c7967c5c81f3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya nne ni kijani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANGI"," userResponse":" RANGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259620346","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259620345"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_190532"," gameId":" f5502bce-a3fd-4f2e-a286-c7967c5c81f3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya nne ni kijani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259621058","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259621058"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_190532"," gameId":" f5502bce-a3fd-4f2e-a286-c7967c5c81f3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya nne ni kijani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NNE"," userResponse":" NNE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259621571","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259621571"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_190532"," gameId":" f5502bce-a3fd-4f2e-a286-c7967c5c81f3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya nne ni kijani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259622293","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259622293"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_190532"," gameId":" f5502bce-a3fd-4f2e-a286-c7967c5c81f3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya nne ni kijani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJANI"," userResponse":" KIJANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259625362","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259625362"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_190532"," gameId":" f5502bce-a3fd-4f2e-a286-c7967c5c81f3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Miwa ni rangi ya kijani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIWA"," userResponse":" MIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259625795","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259625795"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_190532"," gameId":" f5502bce-a3fd-4f2e-a286-c7967c5c81f3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Miwa ni rangi ya kijani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259626288","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259626288"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_190532"," gameId":" f5502bce-a3fd-4f2e-a286-c7967c5c81f3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Miwa ni rangi ya kijani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANGI"," userResponse":" RANGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259626410","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259626410"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_190532"," gameId":" f5502bce-a3fd-4f2e-a286-c7967c5c81f3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Miwa ni rangi ya kijani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259627162","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259627162"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_190532"," gameId":" f5502bce-a3fd-4f2e-a286-c7967c5c81f3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Miwa ni rangi ya kijani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJANI"," userResponse":" KIJANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259630185","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259630185"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_190532"," gameId":" f5502bce-a3fd-4f2e-a286-c7967c5c81f3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya tano ni samawati."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANGI"," userResponse":" RANGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259630297","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259630297"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_190532"," gameId":" f5502bce-a3fd-4f2e-a286-c7967c5c81f3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya tano ni samawati."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259631049","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259631049"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_190532"," gameId":" f5502bce-a3fd-4f2e-a286-c7967c5c81f3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya tano ni samawati."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANO"," userResponse":" TANO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259631422","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259631421"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_190532"," gameId":" f5502bce-a3fd-4f2e-a286-c7967c5c81f3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya tano ni samawati."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259632505","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259632505"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_190532"," gameId":" f5502bce-a3fd-4f2e-a286-c7967c5c81f3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya tano ni samawati."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAMAWATI"," userResponse":" SAMAWATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259635334","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259635334"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_190532"," gameId":" f5502bce-a3fd-4f2e-a286-c7967c5c81f3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbingu ni samawati."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBINGU"," userResponse":" MBINGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259635807","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259635807"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_190532"," gameId":" f5502bce-a3fd-4f2e-a286-c7967c5c81f3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbingu ni samawati."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259636808","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259636808"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_190532"," gameId":" f5502bce-a3fd-4f2e-a286-c7967c5c81f3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbingu ni samawati."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAMAWATI"," userResponse":" SAMAWATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259639679","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259639679"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_190532"," gameId":" f5502bce-a3fd-4f2e-a286-c7967c5c81f3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya sita ni nili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANGI"," userResponse":" RANGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259639811","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259639811"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_190532"," gameId":" f5502bce-a3fd-4f2e-a286-c7967c5c81f3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya sita ni nili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259640383","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259640383"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_190532"," gameId":" f5502bce-a3fd-4f2e-a286-c7967c5c81f3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya sita ni nili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SITA"," userResponse":" SITA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259640646","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259640646"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_190532"," gameId":" f5502bce-a3fd-4f2e-a286-c7967c5c81f3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya sita ni nili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259641259","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259641259"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_190532"," gameId":" f5502bce-a3fd-4f2e-a286-c7967c5c81f3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya sita ni nili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NILI"," userResponse":" NILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259644530","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259644530"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_190532"," gameId":" f5502bce-a3fd-4f2e-a286-c7967c5c81f3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Matunda haya ni ya rangi ya nili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MATUNDA"," userResponse":" MATUNDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259645242","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259645242"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_190532"," gameId":" f5502bce-a3fd-4f2e-a286-c7967c5c81f3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Matunda haya ni ya rangi ya nili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAYA"," userResponse":" HAYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259645774","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259645774"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_190532"," gameId":" f5502bce-a3fd-4f2e-a286-c7967c5c81f3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Matunda haya ni ya rangi ya nili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259645926","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259645926"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_190532"," gameId":" f5502bce-a3fd-4f2e-a286-c7967c5c81f3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Matunda haya ni ya rangi ya nili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259646458","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259646458"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_190532"," gameId":" f5502bce-a3fd-4f2e-a286-c7967c5c81f3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Matunda haya ni ya rangi ya nili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANGI"," userResponse":" RANGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259646590","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259646590"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_190532"," gameId":" f5502bce-a3fd-4f2e-a286-c7967c5c81f3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Matunda haya ni ya rangi ya nili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259647182","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259647182"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_190532"," gameId":" f5502bce-a3fd-4f2e-a286-c7967c5c81f3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Matunda haya ni ya rangi ya nili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NILI"," userResponse":" NILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259650215","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259650215"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_190532"," gameId":" f5502bce-a3fd-4f2e-a286-c7967c5c81f3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya saba ni zambarau."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANGI"," userResponse":" RANGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259650306","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259650306"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_190532"," gameId":" f5502bce-a3fd-4f2e-a286-c7967c5c81f3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya saba ni zambarau."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259651019","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259651019"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_190532"," gameId":" f5502bce-a3fd-4f2e-a286-c7967c5c81f3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya saba ni zambarau."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SABA"," userResponse":" SABA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259651442","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259651442"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_190532"," gameId":" f5502bce-a3fd-4f2e-a286-c7967c5c81f3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya saba ni zambarau."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259652395","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259652395"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_190532"," gameId":" f5502bce-a3fd-4f2e-a286-c7967c5c81f3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya saba ni zambarau."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAMBARAU"," userResponse":" ZAMBARAU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259655409","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259655409"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_190532"," gameId":" f5502bce-a3fd-4f2e-a286-c7967c5c81f3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nguo yangu ni ya kizambarau."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGUO"," userResponse":" NGUO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259655741","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259655741"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_190532"," gameId":" f5502bce-a3fd-4f2e-a286-c7967c5c81f3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nguo yangu ni ya kizambarau."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANGU"," userResponse":" YANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259656464","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259656463"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_190532"," gameId":" f5502bce-a3fd-4f2e-a286-c7967c5c81f3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nguo yangu ni ya kizambarau."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259656526","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259656526"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_190532"," gameId":" f5502bce-a3fd-4f2e-a286-c7967c5c81f3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nguo yangu ni ya kizambarau."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259657588","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259657588"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_190532"," gameId":" f5502bce-a3fd-4f2e-a286-c7967c5c81f3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nguo yangu ni ya kizambarau."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIZAMBARAU"," userResponse":" KIZAMBARAU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259659811","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259659811"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_190532"," gameId":" f5502bce-a3fd-4f2e-a286-c7967c5c81f3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni rangi niipendayo zaidi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259660273","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259660273"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_190532"," gameId":" f5502bce-a3fd-4f2e-a286-c7967c5c81f3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni rangi niipendayo zaidi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANGI"," userResponse":" RANGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259661846","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259661846"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_190532"," gameId":" f5502bce-a3fd-4f2e-a286-c7967c5c81f3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni rangi niipendayo zaidi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NIIPENDAYO"," userResponse":" NIIPENDAYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259662979","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259662979"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_190532"," gameId":" f5502bce-a3fd-4f2e-a286-c7967c5c81f3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni rangi niipendayo zaidi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAIDI"," userResponse":" ZAIDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259665961","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259665961"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_190532"," gameId":" f5502bce-a3fd-4f2e-a286-c7967c5c81f3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je unazijua rangi saba za upinde?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JE"," userResponse":" JE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259667703","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259667703"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_190532"," gameId":" f5502bce-a3fd-4f2e-a286-c7967c5c81f3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je unazijua rangi saba za upinde?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UNAZIJUA"," userResponse":" UNAZIJUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259668175","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259668175"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_190532"," gameId":" f5502bce-a3fd-4f2e-a286-c7967c5c81f3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je unazijua rangi saba za upinde?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANGI"," userResponse":" RANGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259668757","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259668757"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_190532"," gameId":" f5502bce-a3fd-4f2e-a286-c7967c5c81f3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je unazijua rangi saba za upinde?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SABA"," userResponse":" SABA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259669050","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259669050"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_190532"," gameId":" f5502bce-a3fd-4f2e-a286-c7967c5c81f3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je unazijua rangi saba za upinde?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259670062","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259670062"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_190532"," gameId":" f5502bce-a3fd-4f2e-a286-c7967c5c81f3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je unazijua rangi saba za upinde?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UPINDE"," userResponse":" UPINDE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259672783","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259672783"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_190532"," gameId":" f5502bce-a3fd-4f2e-a286-c7967c5c81f3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Je unazijua rangi saba za upinde?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259672849","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259672849"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_190532"," gameId":" f5502bce-a3fd-4f2e-a286-c7967c5c81f3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je unazijua rangi saba za upinde?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UPINDE"," userResponse":" UPINDE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.vow.asc.all.stat.noShow.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259681149","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259681148"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_190532"," gameId":" f5502bce-a3fd-4f2e-a286-c7967c5c81f3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Je unazijua rangi saba za upinde?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.12__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259691215","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259691215"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_190532"," gameId":" addb12a5-14af-4c75-a242-5b6a99b156c8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.12__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_0_8-6-0"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.12__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259696308","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259696308"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_190532"," gameId":" addb12a5-14af-4c75-a242-5b6a99b156c8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.12__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_1_3-1-8"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.12__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259701142","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259701142"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_190532"," gameId":" addb12a5-14af-4c75-a242-5b6a99b156c8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.12__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_2_4-2-9"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.12__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259706243","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259706243"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_190532"," gameId":" addb12a5-14af-4c75-a242-5b6a99b156c8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.12__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_3_7-3-6"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.12__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259712427","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259712426"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_190532"," gameId":" addb12a5-14af-4c75-a242-5b6a99b156c8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.12__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_4_5-9-4"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.12__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259717279","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259717279"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_190532"," gameId":" addb12a5-14af-4c75-a242-5b6a99b156c8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.12__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_5_2-5-8"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.12__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259722149","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259722149"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_190532"," gameId":" addb12a5-14af-4c75-a242-5b6a99b156c8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.12__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_6_5-6-4"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.12__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259727982","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259727981"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_190532"," gameId":" addb12a5-14af-4c75-a242-5b6a99b156c8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.12__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_7_6-1-7"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.12__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259733048","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259733048"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_190532"," gameId":" addb12a5-14af-4c75-a242-5b6a99b156c8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.12__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_8_6-8-2"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.12__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259739360","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259739360"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_190532"," gameId":" addb12a5-14af-4c75-a242-5b6a99b156c8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.12__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_9_2-3-9"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.12__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259745835","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259745835"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_190532"," gameId":" addb12a5-14af-4c75-a242-5b6a99b156c8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.12__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_9_2-3-9"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.vow.asc.all.stat.noShow.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259755303","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259755302"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_190532"," gameId":" addb12a5-14af-4c75-a242-5b6a99b156c8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.12__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_9_2-3-9"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259766349","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259766348"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_190532"," gameId":" 177dd079-04d9-418e-9907-71de053a8447"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamba ana meno makali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMBA"," userResponse":" MAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259766864","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259766864"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_190532"," gameId":" 177dd079-04d9-418e-9907-71de053a8447"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamba ana meno makali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANA"," userResponse":" ANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259767454","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259767454"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_190532"," gameId":" 177dd079-04d9-418e-9907-71de053a8447"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamba ana meno makali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MENO"," userResponse":" MENO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259768303","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259768303"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_190532"," gameId":" 177dd079-04d9-418e-9907-71de053a8447"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamba ana meno makali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAKALI"," userResponse":" MAKALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259771415","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259771415"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_190532"," gameId":" 177dd079-04d9-418e-9907-71de053a8447"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba ana meno makali vile vile."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMBA"," userResponse":" SIMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259771900","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259771900"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_190532"," gameId":" 177dd079-04d9-418e-9907-71de053a8447"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba ana meno makali vile vile."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANA"," userResponse":" ANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259772436","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259772436"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_190532"," gameId":" 177dd079-04d9-418e-9907-71de053a8447"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba ana meno makali vile vile."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MENO"," userResponse":" MENO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259773259","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259773259"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_190532"," gameId":" 177dd079-04d9-418e-9907-71de053a8447"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba ana meno makali vile vile."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAKALI"," userResponse":" MAKALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259773818","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259773817"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_190532"," gameId":" 177dd079-04d9-418e-9907-71de053a8447"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba ana meno makali vile vile."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VILE"," userResponse":" VILE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259774190","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259774190"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_190532"," gameId":" 177dd079-04d9-418e-9907-71de053a8447"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba ana meno makali vile vile."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VILE"," userResponse":" VILE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259777010","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259777009"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_190532"," gameId":" 177dd079-04d9-418e-9907-71de053a8447"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Papa ana meno makali sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PAPA"," userResponse":" PAPA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259777496","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259777495"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_190532"," gameId":" 177dd079-04d9-418e-9907-71de053a8447"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Papa ana meno makali sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANA"," userResponse":" ANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259777973","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259777973"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_190532"," gameId":" 177dd079-04d9-418e-9907-71de053a8447"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Papa ana meno makali sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MENO"," userResponse":" MENO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259778614","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259778614"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_190532"," gameId":" 177dd079-04d9-418e-9907-71de053a8447"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Papa ana meno makali sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAKALI"," userResponse":" MAKALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259779507","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259779507"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_190532"," gameId":" 177dd079-04d9-418e-9907-71de053a8447"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Papa ana meno makali sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259781976","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259781976"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_190532"," gameId":" 177dd079-04d9-418e-9907-71de053a8447"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini baadhi ya wanyama wana meno makali?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259782538","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259782538"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_190532"," gameId":" 177dd079-04d9-418e-9907-71de053a8447"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini baadhi ya wanyama wana meno makali?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINI"," userResponse":" NINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259783221","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259783221"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_190532"," gameId":" 177dd079-04d9-418e-9907-71de053a8447"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini baadhi ya wanyama wana meno makali?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BAADHI"," userResponse":" BAADHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259783393","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259783393"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_190532"," gameId":" 177dd079-04d9-418e-9907-71de053a8447"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini baadhi ya wanyama wana meno makali?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259784132","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259784132"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_190532"," gameId":" 177dd079-04d9-418e-9907-71de053a8447"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini baadhi ya wanyama wana meno makali?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259784536","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259784535"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_190532"," gameId":" 177dd079-04d9-418e-9907-71de053a8447"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini baadhi ya wanyama wana meno makali?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANA"," userResponse":" WANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259785073","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259785073"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_190532"," gameId":" 177dd079-04d9-418e-9907-71de053a8447"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini baadhi ya wanyama wana meno makali?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MENO"," userResponse":" MENO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259786276","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259786276"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_190532"," gameId":" 177dd079-04d9-418e-9907-71de053a8447"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini baadhi ya wanyama wana meno makali?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAKALI"," userResponse":" MAKALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259789441","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259789441"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_190532"," gameId":" 177dd079-04d9-418e-9907-71de053a8447"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ng'ombe ana meno ya nguvu kwa ajili ya kusaga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NG"," userResponse":" NG"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259789457","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259789457"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_190532"," gameId":" 177dd079-04d9-418e-9907-71de053a8447"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ng'ombe ana meno ya nguvu kwa ajili ya kusaga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OMBE"," userResponse":" OMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259789961","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259789961"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_190532"," gameId":" 177dd079-04d9-418e-9907-71de053a8447"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ng'ombe ana meno ya nguvu kwa ajili ya kusaga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANA"," userResponse":" ANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259790614","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259790614"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_190532"," gameId":" 177dd079-04d9-418e-9907-71de053a8447"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ng'ombe ana meno ya nguvu kwa ajili ya kusaga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MENO"," userResponse":" MENO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259790897","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259790897"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_190532"," gameId":" 177dd079-04d9-418e-9907-71de053a8447"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ng'ombe ana meno ya nguvu kwa ajili ya kusaga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259791647","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259791647"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_190532"," gameId":" 177dd079-04d9-418e-9907-71de053a8447"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ng'ombe ana meno ya nguvu kwa ajili ya kusaga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGUVU"," userResponse":" NGUVU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259791983","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259791983"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_190532"," gameId":" 177dd079-04d9-418e-9907-71de053a8447"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ng'ombe ana meno ya nguvu kwa ajili ya kusaga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259792798","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259792798"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_190532"," gameId":" 177dd079-04d9-418e-9907-71de053a8447"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ng'ombe ana meno ya nguvu kwa ajili ya kusaga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AJILI"," userResponse":" AJILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259792862","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259792861"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_190532"," gameId":" 177dd079-04d9-418e-9907-71de053a8447"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ng'ombe ana meno ya nguvu kwa ajili ya kusaga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259793716","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259793715"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_190532"," gameId":" 177dd079-04d9-418e-9907-71de053a8447"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ng'ombe ana meno ya nguvu kwa ajili ya kusaga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSAGA"," userResponse":" KUSAGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259796623","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259796623"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_190532"," gameId":" 177dd079-04d9-418e-9907-71de053a8447"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndege hana meno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDEGE"," userResponse":" NDEGE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259797156","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259797156"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_190532"," gameId":" 177dd079-04d9-418e-9907-71de053a8447"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndege hana meno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HANA"," userResponse":" HANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259797849","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259797849"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_190532"," gameId":" 177dd079-04d9-418e-9907-71de053a8447"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndege hana meno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MENO"," userResponse":" MENO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259800280","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259800280"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_190532"," gameId":" 177dd079-04d9-418e-9907-71de053a8447"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je ndege hula namna gani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JE"," userResponse":" JE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259801303","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259801303"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_190532"," gameId":" 177dd079-04d9-418e-9907-71de053a8447"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je ndege hula namna gani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDEGE"," userResponse":" NDEGE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259801796","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259801796"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_190532"," gameId":" 177dd079-04d9-418e-9907-71de053a8447"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je ndege hula namna gani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HULA"," userResponse":" HULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259802412","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259802412"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_190532"," gameId":" 177dd079-04d9-418e-9907-71de053a8447"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je ndege hula namna gani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAMNA"," userResponse":" NAMNA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259803402","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259803402"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_190532"," gameId":" 177dd079-04d9-418e-9907-71de053a8447"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je ndege hula namna gani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GANI"," userResponse":" GANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259806361","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259806361"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_190532"," gameId":" 177dd079-04d9-418e-9907-71de053a8447"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Panya wana meno ya mbele makubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PANYA"," userResponse":" PANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259806844","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259806844"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_190532"," gameId":" 177dd079-04d9-418e-9907-71de053a8447"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Panya wana meno ya mbele makubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANA"," userResponse":" WANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259807436","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259807436"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_190532"," gameId":" 177dd079-04d9-418e-9907-71de053a8447"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Panya wana meno ya mbele makubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MENO"," userResponse":" MENO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259807659","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259807659"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_190532"," gameId":" 177dd079-04d9-418e-9907-71de053a8447"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Panya wana meno ya mbele makubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259808282","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259808282"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_190532"," gameId":" 177dd079-04d9-418e-9907-71de053a8447"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Panya wana meno ya mbele makubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBELE"," userResponse":" MBELE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259809185","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259809184"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_190532"," gameId":" 177dd079-04d9-418e-9907-71de053a8447"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Panya wana meno ya mbele makubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259809252","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259809252"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_190532"," gameId":" 177dd079-04d9-418e-9907-71de053a8447"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Panya wana meno ya mbele makubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBELE"," userResponse":" MBELE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}